《盲点》前情回顾
Previously on "Blindspot"...
费舍尔总督察员  你来肯定没好事
Chief Inspector Fischer. This can't be good.
我要着手调查大卫·瓦格纳的死因
I'm opening an inquiry into the death of David Wagner.
你永远当不上纽约办的头
You're never gonna be the head of the NYO.
你以为我不知道你一直在暗中活动吗
You think I don't know you've been campaigning internally?
你第一次把机密文件带出联调局
When was the first time you removed classified
纽约办事处是什么时候
documents from the FBI's office?
你当时意识到
And were you aware at the time
你违反了联邦法律吗
that you were breaking federal law?
帕特森是个好探员  她留定了
Patterson is a good agent. She stays.
这是斯隆探员  她会协助我们
This is Agent Sloane. She's going to be assisting us.
奥利维亚·戴利迪奥  生于俄罗斯
Olivia Delidio, Russian-born,
与一名美国人结婚12年
married to an American for 12 years.
你会被指控间谍罪
You'll be charged with espionage,
叛国罪  谋杀从犯
treason, accessory to murder,
幸运的话  也要在牢里待上一辈子
thrown in prison for the rest of your life, if you're lucky.
你收到了什么命令
What are your orders?
我们收到了目标  暗杀目标
We were given targets, people to kill.
-艾莉  -你好  柯特
- Hey, Allie. - Hello, Kurt.
你现在是法警了吗
You're a marshal now?
是  我当时想换个环境
Yeah, I was looking for a change.
我会解开你的绳子  我是来帮你的
I'm going to untie you. I'm here to help you.
我想要答案
I want answers.
你的同事参与了一些非常非常可怕的事
Your colleagues, they're into some very terrible things.
他们是我的朋友
They are my friends.
他们怕你  也确实该怕
They're scared of you, and they should be.
我有任务要交给你
I have missions for you.
都是能让我们更接近目标的事情
Things that move us closer to our objectives.
你向我证明你可以信任之后
You show me you can be trusted, and I'll...
你想知道什么  我都会告诉你
tell you everything you want to know.
俄里翁是什么
What is Orion?
是你死去的地方
Orion is where you died.
那是一次行动
It was an operation.
结果出了岔子  你失踪了
Things went sideways, you went off the grid.
我不明白
I don't understand.
俄里翁使你成了今天这样
Orion is why you're here.
让我们走到了这一步
Why we're all here.
但我不能再说了
But I can't tell you more.
现在不是时候
Not yet.
你不能相信他们
You can't trust them.
他们相信你  所以我也相信你
They trust you, so I trust you.
是你对自己做了这些
You did this to yourself.
偷情归来啊
Walk of Shame, huh?
电影《蒙羞之旅》
我有什么见不得人的
Who said I'm ashamed?
因为你都没让我见过他
Why haven't I met this guy?
你什么时候开始这么关心我跟谁约会了
Since when do you care who I'm dating?
就从你遮遮掩掩开始
Since you started keeping it a secret.
你跟爸爸昨晚怎么样
How was Dad last night?
他还好
He was all right.
就是吃治癌药吃烦了
He's a bit bothered by the cancer meds.
是啊
Yeah.
你们能聊聊我就很高兴了
Well, just glad you guys are talking again.
只靠一个晚期绝症
And all it took was a terminal illness
和一个本以为死了的女孩
and the return of a murdered girl
就把威勒一家重新聚起来了
to bring the Weller family back together again.
不好笑
That's not funny.
是啊  不过多少有点好笑吧
Yeah... I mean, it's a little funny.
反正我觉着好笑
I think it's funny.
一个无辜人
An innocent man
因为你们的行动而死
is dead because of your actions.
你还好吗
Are you feeling okay?
挺好的
Yeah, fine.
不会是因为今天
This wouldn't have anything to do
俄罗斯间谍案进行最后一次庭审吧
with that Russian spy's final arraignment today, would it?
你确定今天要来上班吗
Are you sure you want to be here today?
你不来不会有人怪你的
Nobody would fault you, if you want--
我只想忘掉大卫这档子事
I just want to get past all this David...
我  我只是希望
I... I just want things
能回到之前那样
to go back to the way that they were.
谢谢你们的关心
I appreciate your concern.
你们之前怎么没商量好
How did you not work this out before?
我也是第一次听说  法官阁下
This is the first I'm hearing of this,Your Honor.
那你就是失职
Well, it shouldn't be.
如果你的客户真的知道这个名字
If your client truly has that name,
那就涉及到重大国家安全
it is vital to national security.
-我知道...-给我们一份认罪提议
- I know an... - We'll need a deal on the table
否则我的客户不会多说一个字
before my client says anything further.
给你们十五分钟
You've got 15 minutes.
赶紧商量好
Make it happen.
刚刚是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我是你的律师  你居然都不告诉我
I'm your attorney, you blindside me with this?
虚张声势对你没有一点好...
Bluffing is not going to get you...
我没有虚张声势
It's not a bluff.
在见到法官之前我不能冒险
I couldn't risk the name getting out
以免泄露出去
before I saw the judge.
你真的知道名字吗
You really have a name?
是的  我以我孩子的性命保证
Yes, on my children's lives,
我真的知道名字
I swear to you, I have the name.
你看这能不能帮我脱身
Do you think this could buy me a way out?
嗯
Yeah.
应该可以
I think it might.
我为你的孩子感到抱歉
里面发生什么事了
What's going on in there?
索亚
Sawyer.
你个小傻瓜
You little idiot.
-什么这么好笑  -索亚
- What's so funny? - Sawyer...
这段视频  你看看
This video. Look at that.
莎拉发给我的
Sarah sent it to me.
是索亚的
Of Sawyer.
你有电话打进来
Oh, um, I think you're getting a call.
艾莉
好
Oh, yeah.
我...  好了
I, uh, yeah.
好吧  那我...
Okay, I'll, uh,
在外面等你
I'll see you out there.
好
Okay.
你说什么  什么时候
What? When?
怎么会出那种事
Well, how the hell did that happen?
还有谁知道了
Well, who else knows about this?
不  不  我会处理的
No, no, I'll handle it.
怎么回事
What's wrong?
是局长的电话
That was the director.
奥利维亚·戴利迪奥刚刚在提审时被杀了
Olivia Delidio was just killed at her arraignment.
-凶手是谁  -她的律师
- By who? - Her lawyer.
就在她打算说出
Right before she was about to name
一个俄国情报人员的名字之前
a Russian intelligence source.
她被灭口了
She was being silenced.
那个律师什么情况
What have we got on the lawyer?
律师也死了
The lawyer's dead, too.
我们只掌握了情报来源的位置
All we have is the location of the source.
在哪
Where?
就在这里  纽约办出了纰漏
Here. The NYO has been compromised.
联调局里有间谍
The FBI has a mole.
盲   点
第一季  第十三集
卖国贼就在这吗
The traitor? In here?
局长让我调查
The director wants me to investigate
这楼里的每一个
everyone in the building,
有权进入大楼的人
everyone with access to the building.
如果我们开始四处调查
If we start looking around,
挨个询问  就会打草惊蛇
asking questions, it's gonna raise red flags.
所以我想让你秘密进行
Which is why I want you to handle it, quietly.
我们从杀奥利维亚的凶手查起
We'll start with Olivia's killer.
查出是谁雇佣了她
Work out who hired her.
不是"我们"
Not "We."
是你自己
Just you.
别让任何人知道你的真正目的
No one can know your real objective.
看起来要像常规工作一样
It needs to look like business as usual.
我不会向我的队员说谎的
I'm not lying to my team.
有时你不得不如此
Sometimes you have to.
听着
Look...
我想我们要为这种可能性做好准备
I think we need to prepare for the possibility
那人就是我们中的一员
that it could be one of our guys.
即使他不是
And even if it's not,
内部调查也会引起人心不和
internal investigations are divisive.
你开始调查一件事
You start looking for one thing,
谁知道你会发现什么别的情况
who knows what else you're gonna find?
这么说杀奥利维亚的凶手伪装成了律师
So Olivia's assassin was pretending to be a lawyer?
不  她就是律师
No, she was a lawyer.
玛利亚·布兰特
Maria Blanter.
她在一家由俄国大使馆资助的公司工作
She works for a firm the Russian embassy keeps on retainer.
她是个善后人员
She was a fixer.
奥利维亚显然成了
Olivia was obviously a problem
俄国大使馆中某个人的眼中钉
for someone in the Russian embassy.
玛利亚把她解决了
Maria fixed it.
他说得对
He's right.
那我们要如何证实
So how do we prove it?
如果你们想直接把大使馆
If you want to directly tie the embassy
与犯罪活动联系起来
to criminal activity,
就需要有人在内部接应
you're gonna need someone from inside.
我们确信俄国外交官们正在
We believe Russian diplomats are running
经营一家非法走私集团
an illegal smuggling ring.
可每次我一接近
But every time I get close,
他们就会歇业调整
they shut down and switch things up.
-现在我知道为什么...  -斯隆
- Now I know why... - Uh, Sloane,
能跟你去外面说几句吗
can I talk to you outside for a sec?
斯隆  你在干什么
Sloane, what are you doing?
我听说法院的事了
I heard about the courthouse.
奥利维亚要指证这里的一个内鬼
That Olivia was gonna name an inside player here.
我认为你可能需要些帮助
Thought you might want some help.
别这么看着我
Don't look at me like that.
我是联调局反间谍司的人
I'm FBI counterintelligence.
掌握这些情况是我的工作
It's my job to know these things.
俄国间谍集团还是我的案子呢  记得吗
The Russian spy ring was my case, remember?
好吧
Fine.
别提起内鬼的事
Don't mention the inside man.
你认为是他们中的某人吗
You think it's one of them?
你从大使馆方面调查
Start working the embassy angle.
你守在门口
You stay on the door.
我要有人看守电梯  还有会议室
I need someone on that elevator, the conference room.
杰克逊  看看那边的情况
Jackson, see what's down there.
你俩跟我来
You two with me.
瞧瞧  你果然对你的继任者
Well, you're certainly setting the bar low
要求太低啊  宝芬妮
for your replacement, Bethany.
我一点都不奇怪
Not that I'm surprised.
你给职责办打电话了
Did you call the OPR?
不  不是她  是局长
No, she didn't, the director did.
我得此殊荣  正准备为职责办的
I was just about to give my orientation speech
新晋探员们做迎新会演讲时
for the new OPR agents, a rare honor,
却接到一个电话
but then I get a call
说这个团队再一次  出了纰漏
saying this outfit's been compromised... again.
我是乔纳斯·费舍尔总督察员
Chief Inspector Jonas Fischer,
主管职业责任办公室
Office of Professional Responsibility.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
这个团队从没出过纰漏
This team has never been compromised.
恕我难以苟同
Well, I respectfully disagree.
我在早高峰挤上一辆让人满头大汗的地铁
And I didn't cram myself onto a sweaty train
不是来看联调局又一次
during morning rush hour to watch the FBI
把一起罗伯特·汉森式的间谍案搞砸的
bungle a Robert Hanssen-level breach... again.
我要一个测谎仪操作员
I'm gonna need a polygrapher.
还需要一个嫌疑犯管制区
I'll need a holding space for the suspect,
要公开区域  谢谢
somewhere out in the open, please.
并且我要征用这间办公室
And, you know, I'll use this office
用于后续审问
for follow-up questioning.
乔纳斯  消停会吧
Jonas, let's take it down a notch.
这种情况要谨慎对待
This situation needs to be handled with discretion.
对付这种情况我有经验  宝芬妮
Heh, this isn't my first square-dance, Bethany.
你这样调查
You turn this into a witch-hunt,
会打草惊蛇的
you risk spooking them all.
这件办公室里  许多人行事不负责
This office is rife with irresponsible behavior
且有危险的违法行为
and dangerous infractions, and...
今天我要一个个都揪出来
today, I'm going to find out every last one.
谁给我来杯土耳其咖啡
Someone get me a Turkish coffee?
谢谢麻烦了
Please and thank you.
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell was that about?
他想抢我的位子想了大半年了
He's been angling for my job for the better part of a year.
他想利用这次调查
He's gonna use this investigation
来为难我们  并把我挤出去
to embarrass us and push me out.
我们最不希望的就是他上台
The last thing that we need is that guy in charge.
所以我们要在他之前找到那个俄国间谍
All right, so we got to find the Russian source before he does.
帕特森  把屏幕上的东西关了
Patterson, clear those screens.
怎么了
What's going on?
请不必如此  别因为我耽误你们工作
No, please. Don't let me stop you.
虽然你们正在被调查
Just because you're under investigation as well
你们也可以继续摸索
doesn't mean you shouldn't fumble about
看看能发现些什么
and see what you can find.
等一下  为什么调查我们
Wait, why are we under investigation?
他没告诉你吗
Oh, he didn't tell you?
联调局纽约办事处有个内鬼
The FBI's New York office has been compromised.
我被委派调查此事
I'm here to spearhead the investigation
揪出那个叛徒
and root out the traitor.
你早就知道了
You knew about this?
也许威勒探员有充分的理由不相信你们
Maybe Special Agent Weller had good reason not to trust you.
每个人都有见不得人的秘密
Every closet has its skeleton.
我很期待曝光你们的究竟是什么
I look forward to meeting all of yours.
因为每个人都有嫌疑无一例外
And just to show that no one's above suspicion,
所以威勒探员  你先来
Agent Weller, you're up first.
这是什么
What is this?
我要的是土耳其咖啡
I asked for Turkish coffee.
我们只有这个
Well, that's all we have.
简直展现了你们办事处的水准
What a fitting metaphor for this office's shortcomings.
我们还开不开始了
Are we gonna start this or not?
你是为联邦政府工作吗
Do you work for the federal government?
我们还是绕过这些形式
You know what, we'll skip the formalities
直接来实的吧
and get to the good stuff.
你与同事间曾有过性关系吗
Have you ever had sexual relations with a co-worker?
是的  有
Yes, I have.
该同事是否艾莉森·奈特
Was that co-worker Allison Knight?
是
Yes.
你目前还和奈特小姐在交往吗
Are you currently involved with Ms. Knight?
没有
No.
你与奈特小姐在办事处之外
Did you ever discuss FBI work
谈论过联调局的工作吗
outside this office with Ms. Knight?
是
Yes.
你是俄国间谍吗
Are you a Russian operative?
不是
No.
奈特小姐是俄国间谍吗
Is Ms. Knight a Russian operative?
不是
No.
你现在和其它同事或下属
Are you currently romantically involved
有恋爱关系吗  威勒探员
with any other co-worker or subordinate, Agent Weller?
没有
No.
你知道间谍是谁吗
So... do you have any theories on who it is?
你知道吗
Do you?
威勒没告诉我们会有间谍调查
Anybody else find it weird Weller never told us
你们不觉得很怪吗
about the mole hunt to begin with?
你觉得他怀疑间谍在我们当中吗
Do you think he suspects one of us?
俄国大使馆调查得怎么样了
Where are we on the Russian embassy?
斯隆探员查到三个人  弗拉德·马斯拉克
Okay, so Agent Sloane zeroed in on Vlad Maslak,
斯拉瓦·别列津  伊利亚·阿诺索夫
Slava Berezin, and Ilya Anasov.
都是俄国外交官
All Russian diplomats.
及前俄国国家安全局官员
All former FSB.
他们利用外交豁免权倒腾毒品
They're using their diplomatic immunity to run drugs,
钻石和假钞
diamonds, and counterfeit cash.
你确定是他们
You sure it's them?
确定
Positive.
我拿斯隆探员的原始情报
I took Sloane's raw intel and
进行了复杂的案件分析
ran some complex event processing.
虽然很不容易发现  但我的分析显示
It's subtle, but my analytics show that
当这些人回到俄罗斯
when these guys rotate back to Russia,
倒卖活动就减少了
the smuggling slows down.
斯隆  你在俄罗斯大使馆还有线人吗
Sloane, still have an asset in the Russian embassy?
他还没准备好  我们之间的关系很微妙
He's not ready... my relationship with this guy is delicate.
为什么你不想我们见他
Why don't you want us to meet him?
是担心他会说些什么吧
Worried about what he's gonna say.
我能和你单独说几句吗
Can I have a sidebar?
可以
Yes, you can.
我说他没准备好  他就没准备好
If I say he's not ready, he's not ready.
我必须从长远出发
I have to think of the long game.
如果我们今天不揪出这个间谍
You won't have a long game
你也长远不了
if we don't find this mole today.
我们不能直接去找他
We can't just go down there.
让他去别的地方见我们
Get him to meet us somewhere else.
我们必须充分利用手里的所有线索
We need every lead that we can get.
好吧
All right.
我会联系他
I'll reach out to my guy.
她在故意拖延
She's dragging her heels.
因为她自身难保
Because she's hanging by a thread.
三名间谍死亡  一名平民被杀
Three dead spies and a murdered civilian.
她知道情势如何
She knows how that looks.
你对斯隆探员有多了解
How well do you know Agent Sloane?
不是很了解
Not well enough.
这太荒谬了  整栋楼吗
This is ridiculous-- the whole building?
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
什么事
What's going on?
他们把我们锁在里面了
They're locking us down.
为什么
Why?
我们得到命令  禁止任何人离开大楼
We have orders not to let anyone leave the building.
你没事吧
Hey, you okay?
没事  只是...
Yeah, no, it's just...
连我标配的联调局测谎仪都被调查了
even my standard FBI polygraphs get flagged.
他们查过之后就知道没问题了
And it always turns out fine.
但如果费舍尔想找薄弱点
But if Fischer's looking for a weakness--
谁都知道你在炸弹测试的表现
Everybody knows you bomb tests.
我才需要担心
I'm the one who should be worried.
萨帕塔  我就是那个间谍
Yeah, Zapata, I'm-- I'm the mole.
我进来就是跟你说这事的
That's what I came in here to tell you.
听着  现在是在找出间谍  对吧
Look, we're talking about espionage, though, here, right?
费舍尔肯定要问我们跟谁上了床
Fischer's definitely gonna ask who we're in bed with.
所以呢
So?
等等  你跟谁上床了
Wait, who are you in bed with?
莎拉·威勒
Sarah Weller.
你疯了吧
Are you crazy?
威勒知道吗
Does Weller know?
你得告诉他
You gotta tell him.
你觉得我不想吗
You think I don't know that?
不过话说回来  真要说吗
Here's the thing, though, do I?
里德  他可是威勒
Reade, it's Weller.
你隐瞒了什么  他都会发现的
If you're hiding something, he's gonna find out.
跟你说真是没用
You're no help.
请说出你的名字以便记录
Just... state your name for the record, please.
无名氏
Jane Doe.
真名
Your real name.
泰勒·肖
Taylor Shaw.
我了解到你最近做过这项测试
I understand you've been through this process recently.
这一次  我希望你的回答
This time, I expect your answers
能比"我不知道"更明朗一点点
to be a little more illuminating than "I don't know."
你母亲的名字
State your mother's name.
艾玛·肖
Emma Shaw.
你有曾直接或间接地
Have you ever been directly or indirectly
参与或帮助过恐怖组织吗
involved with or assisted a terrorist organization?
没有
No.
你自己是恐怖分子吗
Are you yourself a terrorist?
-没有  -你是俄罗斯特工吗
- No. - Are you a Russian operative?
不是
No.
你母亲是俄罗斯人吗
Is your mother Russian?
不是
No.
不好意思  你的档案里面说
I'm sorry, it says here in your file
你母亲有八分之一的俄罗斯血统
that your mother is one-eighth Russian.
是记录错误吗
Is that a clerical error?
她八分之七都是英国人
She's seven-eighths English.
但她是俄罗斯人
But she is Russian.
是
Yes.
你是俄罗斯特工吗
Are you a Russian operative?
我是俄罗斯特工吗
Am I a Russian operative?
请回答
Please answer the question.
你是俄罗斯特工吗  是还是不是
Are you a Russian operative? Yes or no.
-不是  -你会说俄语吗
- No. - Do you speak Russian?
-会  -不会
- Yes. - No.
-不会  -你们是否受过
- No. - Are you trained in
俄罗斯军用武术或徒手格斗的训练
the Russian martial arts of Systema or Sambo?
是
Yes.
哪一种  以便记录
Ah, which one? For the record.
应该两种都有
Both, I-I think.
厉害
My.
你有曾把政府财产带离过办事处吗
Have you ever removed government property from this office?
-没有  -是吗  里德探员
- No. - Really, Agent Reade?
一支笔  一盒回形针都没拿过
Not a pen? Box of paperclips?
我拿过一支笔
Yes, I've taken a pen.
你把那件物品拿给其他人用了吗
And did you share that property with someone else?
-是的  -大卫·瓦格纳
- Yes. - David Wagner.
他是  抱歉
Is he... I'm sorry.
他生前是俄罗斯间谍吗
Was he a Russian spy?
-不是  -但他是被俄罗斯间谍杀的
- No. - But he was killed by a Russian spy.
跟奥利维亚·戴利迪奥一样
Not unlike Olivia Delidio.
那  那算问题吗
Is that-- is that a question?
是你下令杀害大卫·瓦格纳的吗
Did you order the death of David Wagner?
不是
No.
你认为你需要为大卫·瓦格纳的死负责吗
Do you feel responsible for the death of David Wagner?
是
Yes.
是你下令杀害奥利维亚·戴利迪奥
Did you order the death of Olivia Delidio
以防止她泄露你是间谍的吗
so she would not reveal your name as a spy?
不是  怎么会  不是
No-- What? No.
她手机里有你的号码
Your number was in her cell phone.
什么意思
Excuse me?
杀害奥利维亚·戴利迪奥的人
Olivia Delidio's assassin,
她的手机里有你的私人号码
your personal cell was in her phone.
你对此是否感到惊讶
Does that surprise you?
是
Yes.
是否对联调局纽约办事处有完全访问权限
Do you have full access to the FBI's New York office?
-是  -没有
- Yes. - No.
没有
No.
你是否有权限接触其设备
Do you have access to its equipment,
文件以及数据库
its files, its databases?
是
Yes.
你跟中情局有联系吗
Do you consult with the CIA?
没有
No.
你是否认识汤姆斯·卡特
Do you know Thomas Carter?
-是  -是
- Yes. - Yes.
不  不算认识
No, not really.
请你用"认识"还是"不认识"来回答
Could you answer yes or no, please?
-你认识汤姆斯·卡特吗  -认识
- Do you know Thomas Carter? - Yes.
你跟局汤姆斯·卡特在中情局共事过吗
Do you work with Thomas Carter at the CIA?
在中情局吗  没有
At the CIA, no.
我重述一下  你跟中情局特工
I'll rephrase-- do you work with Thomas Carter,
-汤姆斯·卡特合作过吗  -没有
- who is a CIA agent? - No.
但你最近经手的一个案子
But you had one case recently
和汤姆斯·卡特的一次行动有过交叉  对吗
that overlapped with one of Tom Carter's operations, no?
是的
Yes.
你最近见过汤姆斯·卡特吗
Have you seen Tom Carter recently?
没有
No.
No!
没有
No.
谢谢  我要问的就这些
Thank you, that's all I need.
科特
Kurt.
怎么了
What's up?
该死
Damn it, um...
我在跟你妹妹交往
I'm dating your sister.
我已经想了好几个星期准备要告诉你
I've been meaning to tell you for weeks.
那你怎么现在跟我说
So you're telling me now?
我知道现在不是好时机  但是
I know-- I know it's bad, it's just...
我不想让你在审讯过程中才知道这件事
I don't want you to find out from some stupid interrogation.
你得取消封锁令
You need to lift the lockdown.
我们得到一条可靠线索  在俄罗斯大使馆
We got a solid lead at the Russian embassy.
叛徒又不在俄罗斯大使馆里
The traitor isn't at the Russian embassy.
她就在这里  在联调局内部
She's right here at the FBI.
你说"她"是什么意思
What do you mean, "she"?
多伊女士  萨帕塔探员
Ms. Doe, Agent Zapata,
梅菲尔助理局长
Assistant Director Mayfair.
测谎仪数据显示  她们三个人说的话
They all had a dizzying number of inconsistencies
都有诸多矛盾的地方
on their polygraphs.
她们每个人都有所隐瞒
Each of these women is hiding something.
我会找出那是什么的
I'm gonna find out what.
他们至少可以把我们关进牢里
They could've at least put us down in holding.
费舍尔就想羞辱我们
Fischer wants us on display.
此刻  他职责办的探员
Right now, his OPR agents
正在把我们的生活搅得一团糟
are tearing our lives apart.
我们的家庭  我们的办公室  我们的电脑
Our homes, our offices, our computers.
他在找什么
What's he looking for?
任何东西
Anything and everything.
他这是冲我来的
This is about me.
他想要我的工作  他关心的才不是内鬼
He wants my job. He doesn't care about the mole.
他只是想让我颜面扫地
He just wants to disgrace me.
你们俩只是刚好被牵扯进来了
You two are just caught in the crossfire.
梅菲尔助理局长
Assistant Director Mayfair?
你对梅菲尔了解多少
So how well do you know Mayfair?
这未免有些巧合
Isn't it a little coinciden--
他在诬陷她们  想要借此升职
He's railroading them. It's a career move.
要没时间了
We're running out of time,
我们需要你把你的情报人员带过来
we need you to bring in your asset.
他行事十分小心
He's hyper-careful.
他不会就这样直接走进联调局
He's not just gonna walk himself into the FBI.
你到底抓住了这家伙的什么把柄
What do you got on this guy, anyway?
罗曼是大使馆的司机
Roman's an embassy driver.
我们在他的手套箱里发现了海洛因
We found heroin in his glove box.
他跟我们合作才免了牢狱之灾
He played ball to stay out of jail.
那你就告诉他你会放过他
So tell him you'll let him off.
我不能那样说
I can't just say that.
说了就意味着要让他彻底脱身了
I'd have to actually let him off the hook.
斯隆  我们需要他
Sloane, we need this.
我尽力
I'll see what I can do.
可是有封锁令  她要怎么把人弄进来
What about the lockdown? How's she gonna get her guy in?
别担心
Don't worry.
我也有人
I know a guy, too.
索尔·格雷罗的卷宗有多处修改
A lot of redactions in this Saul Guerrero file.
你到底涉水多深  宝芬妮
Just how compromised are you, Bethany?
没到会下台的地步
I wouldn't start moving in my things just yet.
黑帮老大
Gang leader,
臭名昭著的联邦线人
notorious federal informant.
在最高警戒的监狱里被杀
Murdered in a supermax penitentiary
而正巧同一时间你在那里探视他
at the exact time you were there to see him.
只是个巧合吗
That's a coincidence?
是
Yes.
你是他的联络人
You were his handler.
或许他发现了什么
Maybe he found out something
你不想让其他人知道的东西
you didn't want other people to know.
如果你手上真的有证据
If you really had something,
我们就不会还坐在这里了
we wouldn't still be sitting here.
我和我的团队都是清白的
My team and I are clean.
看看这个
Look at this.
就像个刚开始学画的小孩的画板一样
It's like a toddler got hold of an Etch A Sketch.
我不擅长做测试
I'm bad at tests.
我知道
Oh, I know.
我把你在联调局的物件都调查了一遍
I pulled all of your standard FBI evaluations.
最令我感兴趣的是这个
What's more interesting to me is this.
你认得吗
You recognize this?
这是一个监控装置
This is a surveillance device,
我需要你把它放进简的安全屋
and I want it inside Jane's safe house.
不认得
No.
我们在你家里发现的
We found it inside your home.
我从来没见过这个东西
I've never seen that before.
也对  我猜你应该也没见过
No, I suppose you wouldn't have.
我的人在一个电灯开关里找到的
My men found it inside a light switch.
像这样的中情局窃听器几乎扫描不到
CIA bugs like this are impossible to sweep for,
但如果了解一般在哪  幸运的话就能找到
but if you know where to look, sometimes you get lucky.
现在的问题是
Now the question is,
中情局为什么要窃听你家
why is the CIA bugging your home?
我不知道
I have no idea.
塔莎  我觉得我们俩已经都清楚了
Tasha, I think we've established
你说谎我是能看出来的
that I can tell when you're lying.
汤姆·卡特想要简的情报
Tom Carter wanted intel on Jane.
我让他死一边去
I told him to go to hell.
他一定是把这个放在我的公寓里
He must've planted this in my apartment
以便寻找要挟我的筹码
to look for leverage.
-他发现了什么  -什么都没
- What did he find? - Nothing.
我想知道他会不会也这么说
I wonder if he'd say the same thing.
但是他现在失踪了  推定死亡
Oh, but he's missing and presumed dead.
真巧啊
That's convenient.
所以情况就是这样  对吗
So that's how it is, huh?
当你有需要的时候才会想起我
You don't call me back till you need something.
来吧  罗曼
Come on, Roman.
谢谢  艾莉
Thank you, Allie.
我欠你一个人情
I owe you one.
可不止一个人情
You owe me multiple.
所以这里到底发生了什么事
So what's going on around here, anyway?
你知道职责办的乔纳斯·费舍尔吗
You know Jonas Fischer from the OPR?
很不巧  我知道
Yeah, unfortunately.
证保计划的名单泄露后我们碰过面  为什么
We met after the WITSEC list leaked-- why?
他正在这里调查内鬼
He's here on a mole hunt.
所以  很不幸地
So, unfortunately,
在他找出来之前谁都不能离开
no one can leave until he finds it.
什么  所以现在我被困在这儿了
Wait, what? So I'm stuck here now.
柯特  你应该早告诉我的
Ugh, Kurt, you could've mentioned that.
很抱歉  如果我说了
I'm sorry, if I'd've mentioned it,
你就不会来了
you wouldn't be here.
好吧  他们有什么怀疑对象吗
Well, do they have any suspects?
梅菲尔  萨帕塔  简
Mayfair, Zapata, Jane.
你觉得会是谁呢
Who do you think it is?
跟她们都没关系
None of them.
所以我们才需要罗曼
That is where Roman comes in.
来吧
Come on.
-进展顺利吗  -是的
- Everything all right? - Yeah.
我只是想让罗曼知道
Just impressing upon Roman
合作的重要性
the importance of cooperating.
你知道对我而言出现在这里
Do you have any idea how dangerous it is
-有多危险吗  -我知道
- for me to be here? - Yes, I do.
所以我才尽量低调
That's why I'm keeping it quiet.
现在你能告诉我雇你开车的那些家伙们的
Now, what can you tell me about the guys
一些情况吗  弗拉德  斯拉瓦  伊利亚
that you drive for-- Vlad, Slava, Ilya?
斯隆说如果我配合  我就能脱身离开
Sloane told me that I'm off the hook if I come in.
没看到书面协议之前我一个字也不会说
Now, I am not talking until I see a deal in writing.
看摄像头
Look at that camera.
这么着吧  你开口
Here's the deal-- you start talking,
要不我就把这张照片发给俄罗斯大使馆
or I send that to the Russian embassy.
你想知道什么
What do you wanna know?
里德探员
Agent Reade.
请跟我来
With me, please.
一切都会没事的
你从一开始就相信无名氏小姐吗  埃德加
Did you trust Ms. Doe initially, Edgar?
不  但她后来赢得了我的信任
No, but then she earned it.
似乎汤姆·卡特也不信任她
Sounds like Tom Carter didn't trust her, either.
实际上  萨帕塔探员告诉过我
In fact, Agent Zapata told me
他为了得到简的情报找过她
that he approached her about informing on Jane.
他也找过你吗
Did he approach you, too?
是的  但是我拒绝了
Yeah, and I said no.
你觉得他在找什么
What do you think he was looking for?
我怎么会知道
I wouldn't know.
结果他偏偏不方便到场回答我这个问题
He's not exactly around for me to ask him that question, is he?
简的运气真好
Lucky for Jane.
对很多人都是好事
Lucky for a lot of people--
卡特的职业生涯里树敌太多
Carter made a career out of making enemies.
这么说你认为他是被谋杀的
So you believe he was killed?
我不相信他是自杀的
I don't believe it was suicide.
卡特和简曾经单独待在一起过吗
Were Carter and Jane ever alone together?
不好说  简要么在家
Well, that'd be tricky-- Jane's either at home,
在工作  要么有安保人员在身边
at work, or with a detail.
但是据我所知
But I was under the impression
梅菲尔助理局长应简的申请
that her detail had been officially lifted
已经正式取消了对她的安保
by Assistant Director Mayfair at Jane's request.
那是在卡特失踪之后
That was after Carter disappeared.
那在此之前  她从没独自外出过是吗
So she never went out without her detail before that?
据我所知没有
Not to my knowledge.
里德探员说  她从没独自外出
Agent Reid says she went out without her detail
不带安保  你跟他的说法相矛盾
all the time-- you're contradicting his story.
不  我没有  那是...
No, I'm not, that's...
里德探员在撒谎吗
Is Agent Reade lying?
你这是在指控他说谎
You're calling him a liar.
我不知道为什么里德会这么说
I don't know why Reade would say that.
他甚至没有
He wasn't even--
简并非每次都不带安保独自外出
Jane didn't go out without her detail all the time.
所以有时候会不带  是吗
Oh, so just some of the time?
帕特森探员  我已经知道她这么做过
Agent Patterson, I already know she did it.
我只需要知道她去了哪里
I just need to know where she went
以及见过谁
and who she saw.
我不...  谁也没见
I don't-- no one.
谁也没见
Mm, no one?
简说过  她  她
Jane said she-- she--
有时候想一个人待着
wanted to be alone sometimes.
无名氏小姐这么说的吗
Ms. Doe said that?
是的  我们曾经出去喝酒  释放压力
Yes, we went out for drinks to blow off some steam.
我理解她
And I get it.
-她的人生太疯狂了  -谁能证明
- Her life is crazy-- - Is there anyone who can account
汤姆·卡特失踪的那天晚上
for Ms. Doe's whereabouts on the night of
简在哪里
Tom Carter's... disappearance?
我可以
I can.
她在这里工作到很晚
She was here at work until late.
随后她在安保的陪同下回家了
And then she went home with her detail.
你刚才还说她甩开了安保人员
You, uh, just said she slipped her detail.
不  安保只是为了保护她
No, it's her protective detail.
她不是犯人
She's not a prisoner.
暂时不是
Not yet.
我只负责开车
All I do is drive.
带他们去会面
I take 'em to their meet-ups.
他们和谁会面  联调局探员吗
Who do they meet? FBI agents?
我怎么知道
How would I know?
又不是人人都带着身份牌
It isn't like anyone's wearing a badge.
我知道你还有所隐瞒
I know you know more than you're saying.
到底谁会开口  你
Who's gonna talk, you...
还是这张照片
or that photo?
好吧
All right, okay.
有一次我听斯拉瓦说  他有内应
One time I heard Slava say he had... inside help.
-他提名字了吗  -没有  我发誓
- Did he mention a name? - No, I swear.
我就待车里  他们做交易时
I stay in the car, I make runs to Akbar's
我会去几趟阿卡巴
when they're making their deals.
我什么都没听到
I don't hear anything.
你要继续嘴硬吗
Are you gonna keep going?
-还是我把它发给...  -但我看到了
- Or shall I send this to... - But I see things.
我看到对方的相貌了
I see people, faces.
我对人的相貌记得很清
I have a very good memory for faces.
很好
Great.
斯隆  带他去实验室
Sloane, take him to the lab.
给他看这里所有探员的证件照片
Show him the photo IDs of everyone who works here.
你确定这样做
Hey, are you sure you're not making this
不会让事情变复杂吗
harder than it needs to be?
最简单的答案通常就是正解
The simplest answer is usually the right one.
简
Jane.
这座大楼里唯独她
She's the only person in this building
整个过去都是未知数
whose entire past is a question mark.
这是针对她的过去  还是我们的
Is this about Jane's past or ours?
听着  无论你对她是什么感觉
Look... however you feel about her,
你不知道她是谁
you don't know who she is.
我只是不想看到你受伤
I just don't wanna see you get hurt.
费舍尔找你
Fischer's looking for you.
所以你说谎了
So, you lied to me.
我问你是否和同事
I asked if you were in a romantic relationship
有恋爱关系时  你否定了
with any of your co-workers, you said no.
但测谎仪不是这么说的
Your polygraph disagrees.
我没说谎
I didn't lie.
我派探员去你家了
I sent agents to your home.
你妹妹不是很配合
Your sister was not particularly cooperative,
但是小索亚
but little Sawyer
很积极地告诉我们
was very eager to tell us all about
他看到你和泰勒阿姨
how he saw you and Auntie Taylor
在你家外面亲嘴
kissing outside your house.
一个吻不代表我们是恋爱关系
One kiss does not mean that we're romantically involved.
这里是不是有点热  威勒探员
Is it getting hot in here, Agent Weller?
我可没穿着三件套西装
I'm not the one wearing a three-piece suit.
至少我们中还有人遵守办公礼节
Well, some of us still respect the formality of this office.
你和敌人上床了
You were sleeping with the enemy.
简不是敌人  而且我们也没上床
Jane's not the enemy, and, no, we're not sleeping together.
真可爱
That's adorable.
我们都是成年人
We're all grownups here.
不要指望我相信
You don't expect me
一个吻之后就没下文了
to believe this just ended with a kiss.
我们没上床
We did not sleep together.
她的安保人员能证实吗
And her detail will confirm that?
-不能  -所以你承认她独自去的
- No. - So you admit she was alone?
是的
Yes.
我们见面
We met...
聊天  之后接吻
we talked, and we kissed.
然后她回家了
And then she went home.
这和调查内鬼有什么关系
What has this got to do with the mole hunt?
你把无名氏小姐送回家了吗
Did you walk Ms. Jane Doe to her door?
没有
No.
所以你没法确定她是否真的回了家
So you can't confirm that she even went home.
等等  我是说
Hang on, what I'm telling you--
我只是想建立一条时间线
I'm just trying to establish a timeline.
帕特森探员说她看到
Agent Patterson told me she saw Jane
简和安保人员回家了
go home with her detail.
你已经证实了她那天夜里
You've just confirmed she subsequently
在没有安保的陪同下和你见面
met you later that night without her detail,
随后她离开了  去了哪里没人知道
after which she left, totally unaccounted for,
同一天晚上汤姆·卡特就失踪了
on the last night Tom Carter was seen alive.
知道简当晚真正去哪儿的人
The only person who knows where Jane really was that night
只有简
is Jane.
如果我说错了欢迎打断我
So, stop me if I'm getting any of this wrong.
汤姆·卡特不信任你
Tom Carter didn't trust you.
他想让你受他监管
He wanted you in his custody.
他会不择手段抓到你
He would stop at nothing to get you.
他对你的生命和任务构成了直接威胁
He posed a direct threat to your life and to your mission.
我没有任务
I don't have a mission.
但问题是
But the kicker is,
你无法解释他失踪当晚
you can't account for the majority of your time
大部分时间你在哪儿
on the night he disappeared.
我可以  我和威勒探员在一起
Yes, I can, I was with Agent Weller,
-然后我  -直接回家了
- and then I went... - Straight home.
是的  你说过了
Yeah. So you've said.
那为什么这些照片
So, why do these photos
显示你在凌晨四点钟时
show you avoiding security cameras
正躲着安全屋的监控录像
at your safe house at 4:00 in the morning?
你没解释窗户里的倒影是怎么回事
You didn't account for the window reflections,
无名氏女士
Ms. Doe.
我睡不着  就去跑步了
I couldn't sleep, so I went for a run.
你在说谎
You're lying.
你吻了威勒探员后  没有回家
You didn't go home after kissing Weller.
你去找卡特了
You went after Carter,
因为他发现了你的秘密
because he found out your secret.
然后你杀了他
And then you killed him.
不  你错了
No, you're wrong.
我不是内鬼
I am not a mole.
你已经暴露了  无名氏小姐
You're caught, Ms. Doe.
我说的是实话  我没有杀卡特
I'm telling you the truth, I didn't kill Carter.
还没人确认卡特已经死亡了
No one's confirmed that Carter is even dead.
你是在确认他已经死亡了吗
Are you confirming that he's dead?
你的测谎结果基本就是条直线
Your polygraph is practically a straight line.
反社会人格都没有你的稳定
I've seen sociopaths with more spikes.
实际上  你五岁时就被绑架
The truth is, you were kidnapped at the age of five.
被贩卖到俄罗斯  他们教你说俄语
You were trafficked to Russia, you were taught the language.
教你如何撒谎  训练你进行战斗
You were taught to lie, you were trained to fight.
再来一次
Do it again.
然后又被送回美国
And then sent back to the United States
渗透进入联调局
to infiltrate the FBI.
里德有所怀疑
Reade suspected it.
但卡特证明了猜测
But Carter proved it.
然后他和帕特森探员的男友
And he and Agent Patterson's boyfriend
正是因此被杀
were murdered because of it.
你就在这间房里
You actually spoke Russian
和一位俄罗斯间谍说过俄语
to a fellow Russian spy in this very room.
奥利维亚·戴利迪奥认出了你
Olivia Delidio recognized you.
但在她说出你的名字之前
But before she could name you,
你的上线派人杀了她
your handlers had her killed.
到此为止了  无名氏
It's over, Jane Doe.
你是不是反而感觉有点解脱了呢
Now, isn't part of you a little relieved?
他认出谁了没有
Has he recognized anyone yet?
没有  这里有超过一千张照片
No. We're dealing with over 1,000 photos here.
看快点  我们没多少时间了
Look faster, we're running out of time.
谢谢你帮我减轻了工作  宝芬妮
Well, thank you for making this so easy for me, Bethany.
简直就像你想让我接管你的职位一样
It's almost like you want me to take your job.
你准备怎么处理她
What're you gonna do with her?
给她点时间
Give her time to consider
让她考虑一下从实招来
making a full confession,
然后再逮捕她
then arrest her.
凭什么逮捕她  你没有实质性证据
Arrest her for what? Your evidence is circumstantial.
没有尸体  没有武器  你只有一张照片
No body, no weapon-- all you've got is a photo.
你在尽力把其他部分
You're trying to twist the rest
曲解成一个你无法证明的故事
into a narrative you can't prove.
你为什么看不清眼前现实呢  威勒探员
Why can't you see what's right in front of your eyes, Agent Weller?
帕特森的实验室里就有一个人
I've got a guy in Patterson's lab
能够认出这个俄罗斯间谍
that can ID the Russian source.
什么人
What "Guy"?
罗曼·科扎  他是斯隆探员
Roman Kozar, a driver that Agent Sloane
从俄罗斯大使馆发展的司机内线
has turned in the Russian embassy.
你有没有想过
Well, have you considered the fact
罗曼·科扎可能会为了
that this Roman Kozar might just tell you
逃避你对他的指控
anything you want to hear in order to get out of
就挑你想听的说呢
whatever charge you apparently have against him?
你到底想不想找到内鬼
Do you wanna find the mole or not?
我已经找到内鬼了
I have found the mole.
不过没关系  我愿意和你的人再确认一次
But fine, I'd be happy to confirm it with your guy.
帕特森探员又一次
And once again, Agent Patterson gives
给一个普通平民看联调局文件
a random civilian access to FBI files.
你是想再害一个你周围的人
Are you trying to get someone else in your
被杀吗
immediate proximity killed?
罗曼还什么都没认出来
Roman hasn't found anything.
还有很多照片没有看
Still have a lot of photos left to go through.
-但只要...  -也许你看的人不对
- But it's just-- - Maybe you're looking in the wrong place.
也许不是探员
Maybe it's not an agent.
你怎么不给他看纽约办新来的顾问的照片呢
Why don't you show him a picture of the NYO's newest consultant?
好吧
Fine.
给他看
Go ahead.
-是她  -不可能
- Her! - No.
我认得她的样子  我见过她
I know her face, I've seen her,
和斯拉瓦在一起  我绝对没认错这些纹身
with Slava-- I would know those tattoos anywhere.
-这不可能  -就是她
- That doesn't make any sense. - It's her.
这非常可能  威勒探员
It makes plenty of sense, Agent Weller,
只要你愿意认清事实
if you're willing to see it.
给局长打电话  告诉他我抓到内鬼了
Call the director, tell him I've caught his mole.
请站起来
Please stand.
简  简
Jane... Jane!
柯特  不是我做的
Kurt, I didn't do this.
我相信你  什么都别和他们说
I believe you, all right? Don't say a thing to them.
我会找出真相的  好吗  你听懂了吗
I'll find out the truth. Okay? You hear me?
-费舍尔查到证据了  -费舍尔错了
- Fischer made his case. - Fischer's wrong.
不是简做的
Jane didn't do this.
-我们要找到真正的叛徒  -柯特
- We need to find the real traitor. - Kurt.
我知道你不想听
Look, I know you don't wanna hear this.
那就别说
All right, so don't say it.
和他们谈谈  拜托
Talk to them, please.
你也这样吗
You too?
俄罗斯外交官给她纹了身
So the Russian diplomats tattooed her,
消除了她的记忆
wiped her memory,
把她丢在时代广场是为了帮他们走私的吗
and dropped her in Times Square to help them smuggle?
她加入我们的时间不久  对他们还没用
She hasn't been with us long enough to be useful to them.
她没有权限获取他们需要的情报
She doesn't have any access to the intel they'd need.
是她的纹身才让我们找到俄罗斯人的
Her tattoos led us to the Russians!
纹身是在帮我们破案  不是犯案
They're solving crimes, not enabling them.
简不是内鬼
Jane is not the mole.
那罗曼为什么指认她
Then why did Roman ID her?
你是对俄罗斯反间谍情报探员
You're a Russian counterintelligence agent.
你有多年时间能破获这间谍组织
You've had years to bust this spy ring.
你却没有  为什么
You didn't, why?
你在保护他们
You're protecting them.
罗曼是你的人
Roman's your guy.
他是在你的指示下说是简的
He ID'd Jane because you told him to.
我这一整天都是在帮你
I have been here all day trying to help you.
我们今天没叫你来
We didn't call you in here today.
你自己来的
You just showed up.
-不可理喻  -是吗
- This is insane. - Is it?
来看看你不在罗曼旁边引导他
Let's see what Roman has to say
他会怎么说
when you're not there to coach him.
给我盯紧了她
Don't let her out of your sight.
-是斯隆  对不对  -什么
- It's Sloane, isn't it? - What?
-你跟我说实话  -什么  什么
- You tell me the truth... - What, what, what?!
说实话
Tell me the truth!
威勒  住手
Weller, stop it!
阿特·特雷维桑
Art Trevisan.
你说你去了趟阿卡巴
You said you make runs to Akbar's?
-他们卖什么  -咖啡
- What do they sell? - Coffee.
哪种咖啡
What kind?
黑色的  泥状的  研磨咖啡豆
The black, sludgy stuff with the-- the grinds.
谁给我来杯土耳其咖啡
Someone get me a Turkish coffee?
费舍尔为职责办的新晋探员们做的迎新演讲
Fischer's orientation for the new OPR agents.
是在哪
Where was it?
纽瓦克  早八点
Newark. 8 a.m.
我正准备为职责办的新晋探员们
I was just about to give my orientation speech
做迎新会演讲时
for the new OPR agents.
却接到一个电话
Then I get a call.
奥利维亚死于早上8:06
Olivia was found dead 8:06 a.m.
局长什么时候打给你的
What time did the director call you?
八点半  他第一个打给我
8:30, I was his first call.
费舍尔在九点之前到的
Fischer arrived just before 9.
我在早高峰挤上一列
I didn't cram myself onto a sweaty train
让人满头大汗的火车
during morning rush hour--
费舍尔不可能在纽瓦克坐上火车
There's no way Fischer took a train from Newark
九点就到达这里
and got here by 9:00 a.m.
除非那个下令刺杀的人给他通风报信了
Unless he was tipped off by the people that ordered the hit.
真是完美的掩护  是不是
It's a perfect cover, isn't it?
费舍尔有职责办的管辖权
Fischer's got OPR jurisdiction.
也就是说  他可以除掉
Which means he can shut down anyone
任何可能找出走私犯的人
that gets close to the smugglers.
费舍尔是内鬼  对不对
Fischer's the mole, isn't he?
回答我
Answer me.
回答我  回答我
Answer me-- answer me--
我不得不撒谎  你听到他说的了
I had to lie, you heard him!
他说他会杀了我
He said he was gonna kill me!
你是想再害一个你周围的人
Are you trying to get someone else
被杀吗
in your immediate proximity killed?
他非常危险
He's a very dangerous man.
如果费舍尔是双重间谍  那他知道简不是
If Fischer's the double-agent, he knows that Jane isn't.
他会在有人证明这一点之前杀她灭口
He'll try to silence her before anyone can prove it.
联调局司法部
联调局囚犯押送
其实我们职责部的拘留所
You know, our OPR detention facilities
还挺舒服的
are actually quite comfortable.
但我觉得你在这儿待不久了
But I don't think you'll be here for long.
你抓错人了  我是清白的
You have the wrong person, I'm innocent.
清白的人有不在场证明
Innocent people have alibis.
卡特被杀那晚  你在哪
So where were you the night Carter was killed?
不是我杀的
I didn't kill him.
也许吧
Maybe not.
只能说明  当天凌晨四点
It only means whatever you were up to
你想要做的事更加邪恶
4 a.m. that morning must've been worse.
我只花了几小时就收集到了指向你的证据
I collected my evidence against you in a matter of hours.
想想看  要是给我几天  几周或几个月
Imagine what I'll find in a few days
我能发现多少
or weeks or months,
你坐在黑暗里  等着接受叛国罪审判
as you sit in a dark hole, awaiting trial for treason.
我要埋了你  简
I'm going to bury you, Jane.
停下  简
Stop! Jane!
联调局  联调局
FBI, FBI, FBI!
联调局  别挡着
FBI! Move it!
他腐化了  简  是费舍尔
He's corrupt! Jane! It's Fischer!
-他是内鬼  -威勒一突破那扇门
- He's the mole! - The second Weller breaches that door,
他就也犯下了叛国罪
he's committing treason as well.
把她关起来
Get her to holding.
我给局长打电话
I'm gonna call the director.
简
Jane!
开门  是他
Open this door! It's him!
我们会阻止他的  让我过去
We've gotta stop him! Let me past.
费舍尔
Fischer!
简
Jane!
等一下
Now... just hang on.
简
Jane!
他想要掏枪
He was going for his gun.
他死了
He's dead.
现在怎么办
So what happens now?
斯隆和她的队友回去逮捕俄国外交官
Sloane and her team are gonna pick up the Russian diplomats.
如果不以走私罪名起诉他们
If they don't go down for smuggling,
我们就以间谍活动和密谋罪起诉他们
we've got them on espionage and conspiracy.
至少
At the very least,
他们会被遣送回俄国
they'll get deported back to Russia.
对今天来说  这就算是胜利了
On a day like today, that's a win.
我想问的是  我怎么办
I meant, what happens to me?
你回家吧
You go home.
你射杀费舍尔的时候
When you shot Fischer,
他想要拿枪
he was going for his gun.
你的生命受到威胁
Your life felt... threatened.
正当防卫
Self-defense.
谢谢你
Thank you...
为我说话  相信我
for standing up for me, for believing me.
你要是想去哪儿的话  我们可以谈谈
If you wanna go somewhere, we can talk about it.
我应该直接回家
I think I should just go home.
好
Okay.
晚安  柯特
Hey, good night, Kurt.
里德
Reade.
你和莎拉是认真的吗
You and Sarah, is it serious?
是的
Yeah.
否则我就不会和她在一起了
I wouldn't be with her if it wasn't.
分手吧
End it.
能听见吗
Can you hear me?
不管是谁在监听我
Whoever's listening to me right now,
我知道你能听见  费舍尔给我看过窃听器
I know you're there-- Fischer showed me the bug.
不如你就别浪费大家的时间
So why don't you just stop wasting everyone's time
直接跟我谈吧
and talk to me?
我就在这呢
I'm right here.
你只需要打个电话
All you gotta do is call.
-这不对  -你无权干涉  柯特
- It's not right. - It isn't up to you, Kurt.
-我男朋友是谁跟你无关  -有关  莎拉
- It is none of your damn business who I date. - It is, Sarah.
-要是里德就有关系  -你不用假扮成
- If it's Reade, it is, okay? - I don't need you
-保护妹妹的好哥哥  -他是我同事
- playing protective older brother, so thanks. - He works with me!
-我没有  -有  你有
- I'm not. - Yes, you are.
我阻止你们不是因为你想的那样
I'm not in the way that you think.
那你倒是说说原因
Then enlighten me, please.
我们这辈子失去了太多人
We've got so much loss in our lives.
妈妈  泰勒
Our mom... Taylor.
爸爸还病了
And Dad's sick.
我问过里德了
I spoke to Reade.
他说你们之间是认真的
He told me things were serious.
-如果那是实话  -是实话
- If it's true-- - It is.
你知道我的工作有多危险吗
Do you know how dangerous my job is?
-那些我不得不承担的风险  -柯特
- The risks that I have to take? - Kurt--
里德的工作和我的一模一样
Reade's job is exactly the same.
我最不希望的就是
The last thing that I want
你或索亚
is you or Sawyer...
失去你们爱的人
to lose someone that you love.
柯特  你不用保护所有人
Kurt, you don't need to protect everyone--
-这就是重点  莎拉  -什么
- That's my point, Sarah! - What is your--
我保护不了所有人
I can't protect everyone!
你知道这有多痛苦吗
Do you know how much it takes?!
我整个人都很痛苦
It takes all of me!
这夺走了我的一切
It takes everything from me!
柯特  出什么事了
Kurt, what's going on?
我不是生你的气
I'm not angry at you. Okay?
要是吵醒他了  我很抱歉
I'm sorry if I woke him up.
你来了
You made it.
你知道我今天有多危险吗
Do you have any idea what kind of danger I was in today?
你究竟为谁效力
俄罗斯人吗
你说什么  俄语吗
What is that, Russian?
除了你告诉我的事
I don't know anything about you
我对你一无所知
except for what you tell me.
而你告诉我的事  我也不能信
And what you tell me, I can't trust.
-你究竟为谁效力  -你知道我在为谁效力
- Who do you work for? - You know who I work for.
别绕圈子了
No, enough of all this circular--
我今天差点被抓
I was almost caught today.
-被威勒吗  -不是  一个职责办的探员
- By Weller? - No, by an OPR agent
他指控我是俄罗斯间谍
who accused me of being a Russian mole.
并怀疑是我杀了卡特
And for killing Carter.
虽然他没全说对
Now, he didn't have all the pieces right,
但也没都说错
but he didn't have 'em all wrong either,
-知道为什么吗  -等等
- and do you wanna know why? - Wait--
因为我就是内鬼
Because I am a mole!
卡特的死我的确有责任
And I am responsible for Carter's murder.
虽然人是你杀的  但归根结底是因为我
You may have killed him, but I-- I am the reason why.
这个职责办的探员  他怎么样了
This-- this OPR agent... what happened to him?
我杀了他
I killed him.
你很清楚自己在为谁效力
You know exactly who you're working for.
不  不是那样的
No, it was not like that.
我别无选择
I-- I had to.
不管你有没有选择
Whether you did or didn't,
你都是我们的一员
you're one of us.
他本打算继续查下去
He would've kept digging, and...
他当时要拔枪
he was reaching for his gun.
现在你的秘密又安全了
And now your secret's safe again.
我们能活下来继续战斗
And we live to fight another day.
我有一个与时间相关的纹身
I have a time-sensitive tattoo
你得让他们注意到
I need you to bring to their attention.
不
No.
你好像没懂
I don't think you understand.
我不干了
I'm done.
我退出
I'm out.
泰勒
Taylor!
你来晚了
You're here late.
有空吗
You got a minute?
把门关上
Close the door.
今天的事让我有点...
Everything that happened today got me...
我不想跳过威勒越级报告
I just don't wanna go over Weller's head.
里德  很晚了  直说吧
Reade, it's late. Out with it.
间接证据也是证据
Circumstantial evidence is still evidence,
费舍尔对简的指控也不都是空穴来风
and Fischer's case against Jane wasn't all that crazy.
她不是俄罗斯间谍
Just because she's not a Russian spy
不代表她没杀卡特
doesn't mean she didn't kill Carter.
那晚她在哪儿
Where was she that night?
我对简的不在场证明
Because I've got some major reservations
有很大的疑惑
about Jane's alibi.
我也是
Me, too.
现在的问题是
The question now is,
我们对此要怎么办
what are we gonna do about it?